waploaded.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy ▷ Waploaded.com

### We take your privacy seriously.

This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it on Waploaded.com Routine Information Collection. All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes, and lets me know what pages and information are useful and helpful to visitors. 

### Cookies and Web Beacons

Where necessary, this site uses cookies to store information about a visitor's preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content. Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies. 

### Controlling Your Privacy

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms. 

### Special Note About Google Advertising

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google's cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google's own privacy policies. 

#### About Google and advertising:

What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. On personally placed adverts on our website (Waploaded.com) sofar advertising fee is paid, there may be no refund for such service, the least may be to extend advertising periods, thats of our server happens to go down during your advertising. 

### Our Hosting Policy.

All Videos On Waploaded Are Hosted On Popular Video Hosting Websites, And Are Licensed To Different Channels. We Only Provide Them For streaming For Our Users By Carefully Under Acknowledging Copyright Rules Copy Them To Our Servers, Musics (Sound Recordings) are only distributed for artiste(s) promotional aim alone, You Can Read Our [Content Removal](http://www.waploaded.com/docs/dmca) if anyOne Holds Bound to Run On Our Platform. 

### Contact Information

Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to an Administrator at info@waploaded.com for further clarification.

1) A word filter has been put in place to prevent forum members from using sexually explicit words in their posts.   
2) Our Members have been informed that they need to keep their words clean if the Website is to survive.   
3) Users upload access for Audio, Videos files has been restricted.   
4) All users acknowledge that they are responsible for anything they post on Waploaded.com 

Written: Aug 23, 2014; Updated: Oct 07, 2016; Read: 18907 times
